Guide to the University Archives Poster Collection, 1935-ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
- Container List
  - Bach: The Six Brandenburg Concerti, 1985 March 21 (2 copies) (Box 3)
  - Martin Walser: Three Lectures, 1985 April 2-4 (Box 3)
  - Anne McDougall Memorial Award Announcement, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Barbershop Harmony Guest Night, 1985 July 15 (Box 3)
  - Winterfest of Contemporary Arts Schedule, 1985 January (Box 3)
  - "Kashmir and Rajasthan: Photographs by Raghubir Singh" Reception, 1985 January 14 (Box 3)
  - The Medium and Three for All Reception, 1985 January 11 (Box 3)
  - Woody Shaw and the Duke Jazz Ensemble Present a Jazz Clinic and Two Performances (Winterfest Event), 1985 January 25-27 (2 copies) (Box 3)
  - Woody Shaw and the Duke Jazz Ensemble Program, 1985 January 27 (Box 3)
  - Three for All and The Medium Program, 1985 January 10-11, 13 (Box 3)
  - Three for All and The Medium, 1985 January 10-11, 13 (Box 3)
  - The Duke Symphony Orchestra Program (Winterfest Event), 1985 January 24 (Box 3)
  - The Ciompi Quartet Program, 1985 January 18 (Box 3)
  - Daniel Halpern Poetry Reading, 1985 January 15 (Box 3)
  - "Duke x 9" Exhibition (Winterfest Event), 1985 January 7-31 (Box 3)
  - Winterfest Schedule, 1985 January (Box 3)
  - Rotterdam Philharmonic, 1985 February 21 (Box 3)
  - An Evening of Indonesian Puppet Theatre, 1985 March 30 (2 copies) (Box 3)
  - Tapestries by Ruth Lang, 1985 March 1-April 4 (Box 3)
  - Holi Celebration, 1985 March 16 (Box 3)
  - Arabic Music Performance and Lecture by George Sawa, 1985 February 8 (Box 3)
  - Duke Artists Series Schedule, 1983-1984 (Box 3)
  - Duke Dance Student/Faculty Recital, 1984 February 2-3 (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1984 February (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1984 March (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1984 April (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1983 December and 1984 January (Box 3)
  - Nina Kay Lowe (soprano) Presents "A Song Recital," 1984 April 1 (Box 3)
  - Gina Bachauer Memorial Piano Master Class with Claude Frank, 1984 January 27-28 (Box 3)
  - Rein de Graaff (jazz pianist), 1984 January 30 (Box 3)
  - Claude Frank and Lilian Kallir (pianists), 1984 January 29 (Box 3)
  - A.K Ramunujan Lecture ("Twelve Indian Poems") and Poetry Reading, 1984 November 29 (Box 3)
  - James Galway (flautist) and Phillip Moll (pianist), 1984 November 1 (Box 3)
  - Duke Dance Annual Faculty-Student Concert Program, 1984 December 7-8 (Box 3)
  - Quadflix Schedule, 1984 Spring Semester (Box 3)
  - Trent Society (Medieval and Renaissance Medicine) Lecture Schedule, 1984 Fall (Box 3)
  - A Dialogue With Hope, 1984 September 23 (Box 3)
  - Yeomen of the Guard (Durham Savoyards), 1984 April 13-14, 27 (Box 3)
  - The North Carolina Symphony, 1984 September 24 (Box 3)
  - The Red Clay Ramblers Play for the Eno, 1983 April 21 (Box 3)
  - Handel's Samson, 1983 April 29 (Box 3)
  - The Houston Symphony Orchestra, 1983 April 19 (Box 3)
  - The Romeros, 1983 February 28 (Box 3)
  - Uto Ughi (violinist), 1983 March 30 (Box 3)
  - Andre Watts (pianist), 1983 February 8 (Box 3)
  - Itzhak Perlman and the Lincoln Center Chamber Music Society with the Ciompi Quartet and Benjamin Ward, 1983 October 3 (Box 3)
  - Patience (The Durham Savoyards), April 15-16, 20 (Box 3)
  - Early Chamber Music Performed by the Fletcher Residents Schedule, 1983-1984 (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1983 November (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Encounters, 1982 November-1983 February (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Encounters, 1983 November, 1984 February and April (Box 3)
  - A Series of Appearances by Charles Rosen, 1983 February 21-26 (Box 3)
  - Quadflix, 1983 Spring (Box 3)
  - Freewater Films, 1983 Spring (Box 3)
  - Marian McPartland in the Mary Lou Williams Jazz Festival, 1983 April 16 (Box 3)
  - Durham Symphony Presents "Pops Americana," 1983 November 17 (Box 3)
  - Senior Day, 1983 May 6 (Box 3)
  - Festival for the Eno, 1983 July 3-4 (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1983 January (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1983 February (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1983 March (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1983 April (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1983 September and October (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1983 November (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1983 December and 1984 January (Box 3)
  - The Durham Civic Choral Society and the North Carolina Chamber Orchestra Presents Samson, 1983 April 29 (Box 3)
  - North Carolina Synergic Theater, 1983 May 19-21 (Box 3)
  - The Blackburn Literary Festival, 1983 March 22, 24, 29, 31, April 5 and 15 (Box 3)
  - Claude Frank and Lilian Kallir (pianists), 1983 February 19 (Box 3)
  - The Ciompi Quartet, 1982 October 23, 1983 January 30 and March 19 (Box 3)
  - Ark Dances, 1983 March 24-25, 27 (Box 3)
  - The Zagreb Grand Ballet of the Croatian National Theatre Program, 1982 November 19 (Box 3)
  - The Bach Aria Group Program, 1982 November 3 (Box 3)
  - The Edward Tarr Brass Ensemble Program, 1982 October 21 (Box 3)
  - Michael Best (tenor) Program, 1982 January 21 (Box 3)
  - I Nuovi Virtuosi Di Roma Program, 1982 February 17 (Box 3)
  - Abelard and Heloise Program, 1982 February 23 (Box 3)
  - Jean-Pierre Rampal (flute) Program, 1982 March 24 (Box 3)
  - Die Fledermaus (The National Opera Company) Program, 1982 April 6 (Box 3)
  - Edward Tarr Brass Ensemble, 1982 October 21 (2 copies) (Box 3)
  - Ethnomusicology at Duke Lectures: Dr. Robert C. Provine (November 10) and Dr. Regula Burckhardt Qureshi (November 15), 1982 (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Encounters, 1982 January 16, 28 and March 1 (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Lectures, 1981-1982 (Box 3)
  - The Duke University Chapel Choir and Orchestra Presents The Passion According to John, 1982 March 28 (Box 3)
  - The Durham Civic Choral Society and The North Carolina Chamber Players Present "An Afternoon of Haydn," 1982 March 14 (Box 3)
  - Pygmies, An Epic of the Golden Age (documentary), 1982 October 25 (Box 3)
  - West Side Story (Hoof 'N' Horn), 1982 April 1, 3-5 and May 7-8 (Box 3)
  - Wendy Jaffe (piano) and Richard Hofmann (trumpet) Student Recital, 1982 April 4 (Box 3)
  - Concerts of Early Chamber Music on Original Instruments, 1982-1983 (Box 3)
  - Meg Christian and Marie Rhines, 1982 May 14 (Box 3)
  - Employee Awards Banquet Auditions, 1982 April 14-16 (Box 3)
  - The Ciompi Quartet, 1981 November 7, 1982 January 31 and March 27 (Box 3)
  - Quad Flicks, 1982 Spring (Box 3)
  - Quad Flicks, 1982 Fall (Box 3)
  - Gustav Leonhardt Lectures and Recitals, 1982 October-November (Box 3)
  - Summer Theater at Duke, 1982 June 3-July 24 (Box 3)
  - Mikado (Durham Savoyards), 1982 April 23-24 (Box 3)
  - Duke University Union All Nighter, 1982 March 19 (Box 3)
  - Jorma Kaukonen, 1982 March 4 (Box 3)
  - Jean-Pierre Rampal (flute), 1982 March 24 (Box 3)
  - Summer Theater at Duke (brochure), 1982 June 3-July 24 (Box 3)
  - The Archive Call for Submissions, 1982 January 29 (Box 3)
  - Nursing Awareness Week, 1982 September 19-24 (Box 3)
  - Duke University Calendar, 1982-1983 (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1981 December-1982 January (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1982 February (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1982 March (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1982 April (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1982 November (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1982 December (Box 3)
  - The Canadian Brass Program, 1981 October 19 (Box 3)
  - The Feld Ballet Program, 1981 November 12-13 (Box 3)
  - "Painting in Color: Works by Thomas E Link," 1981 June 8-July 31 (2 copies) (Box 3)
  - Cultural Arts Festival, 1981 January 29 (Box 3)
  - George Heard Hamilton on "Vision and Time: Aspects of French Art 1870-1920," 1981 October-November (Box 3)
  - Virtuoso Players, 1981 November 1 (2 copies) (Box 3)
  - Gerard Verbeke on "Avicenna's Metaphysics and the West," 1981 March 19 (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Art Spring Lecture Series, 1981 March-April (Box 3)
  - The Lionel Stevenson Essay Contest, 1981 March 27 (Box 3)
  - The Pitchforks Present "Jambo-81," 1981 March 21 (Box 3)
  - "Water Pictures," by Penelope Maunsell, 1981 July 13-August 14 (Box 3)
  - Arts in the Church Conference, 1981 May 18-22 (Box 3)
  - Freewater Films Schedule, 1981 Summer (Box 3)
  - Quad Flicks, 1981 Fall (Box 3)
  - A Celebration of the Music of Vincent Persichetti, 1981 October 26 and 28 (Box 3)
  - Barbara Cook in Concert, 1981 October 9 (Box 3)
  - "Musique D'Apres-Midi," 1981 December 3 (2 copies) (Box 3)
  - Quad Flicks, 1981 Summer (2 copies) (Box 3)
  - Julianne Swanson Hull (Artsfare Presentation), 1981 May 16 (Box 3)
  - "Menage ad infinitum" Exhibition, 1981 June 5-7 (Box 3)
  - Imperfect Triangles (Summer Stage), 1981 June 25-27, 30 and July 1-3 (Box 3)
  - "A Recital of Flute and Strings" (Artsfare Presentation), 1981 May 28 (Box 3)
  - Artsfare (Summer Festival of Arts) Schedule, 1981 (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1981 January (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1981 February (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1981 April (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1981 September and October (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1981 December and 1982 January (Box 3)
  - "A Conference on Canadian Federalism," 1981 November 8 (Box 3)
  - The 1981 William Blackburn Literary Festival, 1981 March-April (Box 3)
  - Rites of Spring, 1981 May 6 (Box 3)
  - Robert Parkins Organ Recital (Artsfare Presentation), 1981 June 2 (Box 3)
  - North Carolina Symphony, 1981 September 30 (Box 3)
  - "Computeraction: A Symposium on Computer-Aided Design," 1981 September 25-27 (Box 3)
  - Allen Dean Organ Recital, 1980 February 24 (Box 3)
  - Latent Image Request for Submissions, 1980 (Box 3)
  - "Be Jubilant My Feet: A Celebration of Dance As Religious Expression," 1980 May 19 (Box 3)
  - Reynolds Price, 1980 June 19 (Box 3)
  - North Carolina Dance Theater, 1980 December 1-2 (Box 3)
  - "The Museum Crafts Collection 1980," July 7-August 2 (Box 3)
  - Herbert Buffington and Fay Freed Organ Recital,1980 March 17 (Box 3)
  - Jewish Arts Festival Guide, 1980 April 3-12 (Box 3)
  - H.M.S. Pinafore (Durham Savoyards), 1980 April 18-19 (Box 3)
  - Pauline Koner Dance Performance and Master Class, 1980 March 28-29 (Box 3)
  - Francis Perry Recital, 1980 July 31 (Box 3)
  - The Triangle Dance Guild 1979-1980 Season (Box 3)
  - Arts in the Church Conference, 1980 May 19-23 (Box 3)
  - 50th Anniversary Duke Artists Series, 1980 (Box 3)
  - Freewater Films, 1980 Fall (Box 3)
  - A Choral Offering (The Durham Civic Choral Society), 1980 April 20 (Box 3)
  - Bette Elliott Art Exhibition, 1980 September 7-October 3 (Box 3)
  - Dr. Juanita Kreps, 1980 September 15 (Box 3)
  - Don Pasquale (The National Opera Company), 1980 October 7 (Box 3)
  - Take Back the Night March, 1980 April 18 (Box 3)
  - Jean Kilbourne on "The Naked Truth: Advertising's Image of Women," 1980 September 29 (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1980 January and February (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1980 March (Box 3)
  - The North Carolina Chamber Players Recital Series and Pops Festivals (Artsfare Presentation), 1980 June (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1980 September and October (Box 3)
  - Claude Howell Art Exhibition, 1980 October 5-31 (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1980 December (Box 3)
  - The Blackburn Literary Festival, 1980 March 24-29 (Box 3)
  - Freewater Films, 1980 Spring (Box 3)
  - Sea Level, 1980 November 7 (Box 3)
  - Abba Eban, 1980 April 10 (Box 3)
  - Gertrude Stein Gertrude Stein Gertrude Stein, 1980 November 14 (Box 3)
  - "Hear Our Voices: A Gospel Festival" (The Modern Black Mass Choir of Duke University and The East Carolina University Choir), 1980 February 9 (Box 3)
  - Loren Withers (piano), 1980 February 22 (Box 3)
  - The Durham Symphony Orchestra, 1980 June 8 (Box 3)
  - Springfest, 1980 April 11 (Box 3)
  - Duke University Piano Festival with Murray Perahia (program), 1979 October 19-22 (Box 3)
  - Schuyler Robinson Organ Recital (Artsfare Presentation), 1979 May 27 (Box 3)
  - John Hanks (tenor) Presents "John Hanks and Friends," 1979 November 3 (Box 3)
  - New Performing Dance Company (program), undated (Box 3)
  - Francis Perry (Artsfare Presentation), 1979 May 11 (Box 3)
  - The New Performing Dance Company Summer Classes, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Duke University Opera Festival, 1979 June 10, 17, 24 and July 1 (2 copies) (Box 3)
  - Summer Theatre at Duke, 1979 (Box 3)
  - The Triangle Dance Guild 1979-1980 Season (Box 3)
  - Freewater Films, 1979 Summer (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1979 December (Box 3)
  - Quadrangle Pictures, 1979 Summer (Box 3)
  - Quadrangle Pictures, 1979 Fall (Box 3)
  - Freewater Films, 1979 Fall (Box 3)
  - Dick Cavett, 1979 October 5 (Box 3)
  - Howard Thurman and Deborah Partridge Wolfe Lecture Schedule, 1979 January-February (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1979 April and May (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1979 March (Box 3)
  - Dance Black Presents, "Kuumba," 1979 March 6 (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1979 February (Box 3)
  - Duke University Calendar, 1979-1980 (Box 3)
  - Summer Theatre at Duke Summer Season, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Murray Perahia, 1979 October 19 (Box 3)
  - Shirley Frey McConahay Soft Sculpture Exhibition, 1979 June 3-July 30 (Box 3)
  - Rudolph Kremer on "The Classical Italian Organ," 1978 September 25 (Box 3)
  - Fred Raimi, Jane Hawkins and Giorgio Ciompi Recital, 1978 September 16 (Box 3)
  - Robert Parkins (harpsichord) Recital "Three Centuries of Spanish Keyboard Music," 1978 September 30 (Box 3)
  - The Ciompi Quartet, 1978 April 18 (Box 3)
  - Freewater Films, 1978 Summer (Box 3)
  - Lynn Igoe and Frank Smullin Exhibition, 1978 February 19-March 16 (Box 3)
  - Joan Lippincott Organ Recital, 1978 February 19 (Box 3)
  - Springfest, 1978 April 14 (Box 3)
  - The Triangle Dance Guild 1978-1979 Season (Box 3)
  - Duke University Calendar, 1978-1797 (Box 3)
  - The Triangle Dance Guild 1977-1978 Season (Box 3)
  - Henry Kyemba on "A State of Blood: The Inside Story of Idi Amin," 1978 February 14 (2 copies) (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1978 December and 1979 January (Box 3)
  - The Pirates of Penzance (Durham Savoyards), 1978 April 21-22 (Box 3)
  - Duke University Calendar, 1977-1978 (Box 3)
  - The Duke University Wind Symphony Garden Concert, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Un Giorno di Regno (The National Opera Company), 1978 November 3 (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1978 October (Box 3)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1978 November (Box 3)
  - "Windows to Spring" Fashion Show, 1978 January 30 (Box 3)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 1978 February 21 (Box 3)
  - The National Opera Company Presents Don Pasquale (June 25), Martha (July 2), The Barber of Seville (July 9) and Carmen (July 16), 1978 (Box 3)
  - Piedmont Chamber Orchestra, 1978 October 31 (Box 3)
  - Faculty Voice Recital: Katherine Kaufman-Posner (soprano) and John Ruggero (piano), 1977 February 5 (Box 3)
  - Toni Morrison Reading, 1977 April 16 (Box 3)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theater, 1977 February 10 (Box 3)
  - Ken Feit Presents "Itinerant Fool" and "Uncle Billy's Pocket Circus," 1977 March 31 (Box 3)
  - Loren Withers Lecture-Recital on Liszt's Sonata in B-Minor, 1977 March 21 (Box 3)
  - La Traviata (Canadian Opera Company), 1977 February 18 (Box 3)
  - Baroque Concert, 1977 February 20 (Box 3)
  - The Duke Jazz Ensemble and the UNC-CH Jazz Lab Band, 1977 February 8 (Box 3)
  - The Duke Collegium Musicum, 1977 March 20 (Box 3)
  - Sharon Locke Senior Recital (piano), 1977 April 25 (Box 3)
  - Mary Turner Faculty Recital (piano), 1977 April 23 (Box 3)
  - The Duke University Wind Symphony, 1977 April 18 (Box 3)
  - Walter Saul Recital (piano), 1977 April 26 (Box 3)
  - Leningrad Symphony Orchestra, 1977 February 23 (Box 3)
  - Marcia Gillespie on "Media as Propaganda," 1977 February 22 (Box 3)
  - Dance Black Spring Recital "Essence of Black," 1977 February 17 (Box 3)
  - The Beethoven Symposium, 1977 April 14-16 (2 copies) (Box 3)
  - Dr. Raymond Moody on "Reflections on Life After Life," 1977 March 28 (2 copies) (Box 3)
  - A Symposium on Literature and Psychology, 1977 March 25 (Box 3)
  - Portia Turner (soprano) Senior Recital, 1977 March 26 (Box 3)
  - Alger Hiss on "The McCarthy Era," 1977 March 22 (Box 3)
  - Lee Jones (string bass) Recital, 1977 April 19 (Box 3)
  - The Barber of Seville (The National Opera Company), 1977 January 28 (Box 3)
  - "By Faith…The Word Became Flesh: A Celebration of Scripture," 1977 March 24-26 (Box 3)
  - Hearts and Minds (film), 1977 April 4 (Box 3)
  - Karl Shapiro Poetry Reading, 1977 March 24 (Box 3)
  - On Stage: An Evening with Charles R. Wright, Jr., 1977 April 22 (Box 3)
  - A Women's Forum on Finance and Business Careers, 1977 March 26 (Box 3)
  - "Ampitheno" Outdoor Theatre, 1977 June-August (Box 3)
  - Loblolly (Summer Performing Arts Program) Design Contest, 1977 (Box 3)
  - Proctor and Bergman, 1977 November 16 (Box 3)
  - Freewater Films, 1977 Fall (Box 3)
  - A Benefit Concert (The North Carolina Chamber Players and The Durham Civic Choral Society), 1977 October 23 (Box 3)
  - "Sinfonia," 1977 August 5 (Box 3)
  - "An Evening of French Chamber Music," 1977 July 25 (Box 3)
  - Grease, 1977 November 18 (Box 3)
  - The Birmingham Ballet, 1976 November 12 (2 copies) (Box 3)
  - Boaz Sharon (piano), 1976 October 29 (Box 3)
  - Sonata Recital by Dorothy Gilmore (cello) and Frances Evans (piano, harpsichord), 1976 November 15 (Box 3)
  - A Faculty Flute Recital by Barbara Fecteau, 1976 October 31 (Box 3)
  - The Ciompi Quartet, 1976 October 30 (Box 3)
  - Triangle Dance Guild 1976-1977 Season Presents "Four Great Dance Companies" (2 copies) (Box 3)
  - Thomas A. Moore (tenor) Recital, 1976 September 21 (Box 3)
  - Summer Theater at Duke Auditions, 1976 April 19-20 (2 copies) (Box 3)
  - Summer Theater at Duke Schedule, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Alicia De Larrocha, 1976 December 2 (2 copies) (Box 3)
  - Ballet Nacional De Festivales De Espana, 1976 November 21 (Box 3)
  - Lazar Berman, 1976 October 7 (Box 3)
  - A Duo Recital: Dorothy Kitchen (violin) and Kathryn Huestis (piano), 1976 October 10 (Box 3)
  - The Duke Collegium Musicum Present a Program of Renaissance Music for Voices, Strings, and Winds, 1976 November 14 (Box 3)
  - The Duke University Chorale, 1976 November 5 (Box 3)
  - The Duke Jazz Ensemble, 1976 December 7 (Box 3)
  - East Campus Activities Week, 1976 October 24-31 (Box 3)
  - "A Recital of Songs of Three Centuries" by Louis Auld (baritone) and Frances Evans (harpsichord and piano), 1976 September 16 (Box 3)
  - Duke Artists Series Presents The Birmingham Ballet (November 12) and Peter and the Wolf (November 11), 1976 (Box 3)
  - The Clarion Wind Quintet, 1976 February 16 (Box 3)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra Concerto Concert, 1976 April 14 (Box 3)
  - Tom Clark Organ Concert, 1976 April 11 (Box 3)
  - The Duke University String School Spring Concert, 1976 May 1 (Box 3)
  - Robert Parkins Harpsichord Recital, 1976 February 13 (Box 3)
  - A Duo Recital: Bruce Plumb (viola) and Barbara Lister-Sink (piano), 1976 March 21 (Box 3)
  - A Recital by Faculty Members of the N.C. School of the Arts, 1976 April 11 (Box 3)
  - A Duo Recital: Meredith Marcellus (mezzo-soprano) and Wayne Lail (baritone), 1976 April 2 (Box 3)
  - The Duke University Wind Symphony Spring Concert, 1976 March 26 (Box 3)
  - A Faculty Recital: John Ruggero (pianist), 1976 April 15 (Box 3)
  - "String Music by David Maves," 1976 April 17 (Box 3)
  - David Duke and Debbie Atkins Organ Recital, 1976 April 10 (Box 3)
  - Patricia Goodson Senior Piano Recital, 1976 March 30 (Box 3)
  - "Easter Monday Vespers and the Peregrinus Play" (Duke Collegium Musicum), 1976 March 28 (Box 3)
  - The Ciompi Quartet, 1976 March 27 (Box 3)
  - Duke Student Chamber Orchestra, 1976 April 9 (Box 3)
  - Southeastern Institute of Medieval and Renaissance Studies Public Lectures, 1976 July-August (Box 3)
  - Duke University Chorale, 1976 April 8 (Box 3)
  - "Celebration Music for Voices and Instruments," 1976 February 22 (Box 3)
  - Duke University Chorale Southern Tour (March 5-15, 18) and Spring Concert (March 19), 1976 (Box 3)
  - The Jeremy North Student Book Collecting Contest, 1976 March 30 (Box 3)
  - Lazar Berman, 1976 February 12 (Box 3)
  - "Guitar Music, Jazz and Classical: David Feinman Senior Recital," 1976 December 8 (Box 3)
  - Hedrick Smith on "Russian and the Russian People," 1976 April 9 (Box 3)
  - P.J. O'Rourke on "The New Humor," 1976 February 17 (Box 3)
  - "An Evening of New Music by Martin Herman and Lee Calhoun," 1976 April 12 (Box 3)
  - A Jazz Concert, 1976 April 16 (Box 3)
  - Juliana Markova (pianist), 1976 February 27 and 29 (Box 3)
  - Dizzy Gillespie, The Mitchell-Ruff Duo and The Duke Jazz Ensemble in Concert, 1976 February 19 (Box 3)
  - box 4 (Box 4)
  - Duke University Hospital North, undated (Box 4)
  - Duke Chapel, Interior, undated (Box 4)
  - Duke Chapel, Exterior, undated (Box 4)
  - Duke Chapel, Overhead View, undated (Box 4)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1970 September 24 (Box 4)
  - Duke University Chorale, undated (Box 4)
  - Ten Ten, (no year) March 14 (Box 4)
  - Terry Sanford for U.S. Senate, undated (Box 4)
  - Duke University Chorale, (no year) October 15 (Box 4)
  - Duke University Poster (2 copies each of 4 different colors) (Box 4)
  - Lt. General Lewis B. Hershey on "The College Student and the Draft," 1967 February 13 (Box 4)
  - World Law or World War, 1948 November 17 (Box 4)
  - William Butler Yeats Centennial Celebration, 1965 November 16-18 (Box 4)
  - 2nd Annual Mary Lou Williams Jazz Festival, (no year) April 13-16 (Box 4)
  - Artur Rubinstein, (no year) February 15 (2 copies) (Box 4)
  - Hadrian VII, (no year) January 14 (Box 4)
  - Dr. Anne Scott on "A Modest Proposal for a Quiet Revolution," 1966 April 20 (Box 4)
  - The Royal Winnipeg Ballet, (no year) November 5 (Box 4)
  - Carolyn Kizer Reading from Knock Upon Silence, 1965 December 2 (Box 4)
  - A Wilde Evening…With Shaw, 1966 April 7 (Box 4)
  - Duke Study Abroad Information, 1966 Summer (Box 4)
  - President Douglas M. Knight's Convocation Address on "The University: Community and Individual," 1966 September 21 (Box 4)
  - 1966 Film Festival, 1966 April 17-18 (Box 4)
  - Steve Addiss and Bill Crofut present "Songs and Music from Around the World," 1966 February 11 (Box 4)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 1966 March 7 (Box 4)
  - An Evening of Jazz featuring The Billy Taylor Trio and The Roland Kirk Quartet, 1968 November 9 (Box 4)
  - Jacques Loussier Trio, 1972 April 7 (2 copies) (Box 4)
  - The Wonderful O, 1972 May 7 (Box 4)